<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Curriculum on TCFNSW</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Curriculum on TCFNSW</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2019 TCFNSW</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NSW curriculum review interim report: First impressions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/2019curriculum-review-interim-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/2019curriculum-review-interim-report/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This article is the opinion of the author and does not necessarily reflect that of all Teachers&#39; Christian Fellowship members.
NSW curriculum review interim report: First impressions The overriding impression of this interim report is that change is about to occur which reduces the content of the curriculum in favour of improving the ways students learn and their skills for life and employment. The key features are the construction of the curriculum in attainment levels that are independent of age and grade with a focus on the school assessment of achievement, including in senior years modules of new advanced and vocational courses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum versus pedagogy: Does it have to be?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/curriculum-vs-pedagogy-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/curriculum-vs-pedagogy-2019/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This article is the opinion of the author and does not necessarily reflect that of all Teachers&#39; Christian Fellowship members.
Introduction – the issues Just a couple of years ago, the Australian curriculum was endorsed for implementation and already NSW is having a curriculum review. There are many reasons for a review including:
  inadequacies within the Australian curriculum;  the concerns of teachers about overcrowding in the curriculum;  the effects of prescribed curriculum on pedagogy;  the excessive focus on NAPLAN tests and the skewing of both the curriculum and pedagogy to meet community expectations about improving standards in literacy and numeracy;  the data from international testing instruments showing that Australian schools are falling behind other nations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a curriculum for whole individuals and society</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/mcgaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/mcgaw/</guid>
      <description>Building a curriculum for whole individuals and society. Barry McGaw, Chair, National Curriculum Board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there a place for service learning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/place-of-service-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/place-of-service-learning/</guid>
      <description>Breaking the mould: Is there a place for service learning in the revised NSW curriculum?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K-10 History – The devil isn’t in the detail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/history-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/history-devil/</guid>
      <description>K-10 History: The devil isn&amp;rsquo;t in the detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendation on the Modern History Stage 6 Draft Syllabus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/history-recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/history-recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Draft Senior Modern History Syllabus - Recommendations. Alec Mills draws presents some recommendations about Aboriginal education contexts in the Draft Stage 6 Modern History Syllabus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission to NSW Curriculum Review by the Teachers&#39; Christian Fellowship of New South Wales (TCFNSW)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/submission-curriculum-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/submission-curriculum-review/</guid>
      <description>Submission to NSW Curriculum Board by TCF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The devil isn’t in the detail. A response regarding the history national curriculum</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/response2devil-not-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/response2devil-not-detail/</guid>
      <description>K-10 History: The devil isn&amp;rsquo;t in the detail: A response by Alec Mills</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The history debates: Will they never end?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/histdebat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/curriculum/histdebat/</guid>
      <description>The history debates: Will they never end?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>